Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Photography and Photographic Formats
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Prints by Male Photographers, circa 1860-circa 1930; Series V; 6.9; (27 boxes)
  - Photographs by Photographers Outside the United States
    - Oversize Photographic Prints
      - Lebanon
        - Bonfils, Felix (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1806)
      - Russia
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1807)
      - Scotland
        - James Valentine & Co. (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1808-1809)
      - Sweden
        - Ewald, Gustaf (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1810)
- Photographic Prints by Subject, circa 1855-circa 1950; Series VI; 3.1; (8 boxes)
  Series VI is organized into two subseries: Photographs of Celebrities and Photographic Prints of Children.
  This series includes groups of photographs compiled by Palmquist on particular subjects including depictions of celebrities and children.
  - Photographs of Celebrities
    This subseries includes photographs of persons broadly identified by Palmquist as celebrities, including actors, actresses, politicians, and circus performers, as well as groups of individuals, including persons of the same ethnicity or occupation.
    Arranged geographically and then alphabetically by photographer, followed by unidentified photographers.
    - California
      - Bradley & Rulofson, San Francisco, Ulysses S. Grant (Box 139, Folder 1811)
      - Bradley & Rulofson, San Francisco, Jim Smith, a telegraph operator in Carson City, Nevada (Box 139, Folder 1812)
      - Bradley & Rulofson, San Francisco, Little person with birdcage (Box 139, Folder 1813)
      - Bernard, Bruno, Hollywood, Man with cigarette (Box 139, Folder 1814)
      - Carpenter, Los Angeles, Dorothy Gish (Box 139, Folder 1815)
      - Carpenter, Los Angeles, Lillian D. Gish (Box 139, Folder 1816)
      - Cramer, C. L., San Francisco, Two Asian boys (Box 139, Folder 1817)
      - Davidson, Visalia, Will Stuart, mime (Box 139, Folder 1818)
      - Dickman, Sacramento, John C. Fremont (Box 139, Folder 1819)
      - Elite Studio, Los Angeles, Ben Slimbridge (Box 139, Folder 1820)
      - Eureka Studio, San Francisco, Lillian Smith, "Champion Rifle Shot" (Box 139, Folder 1821)
      - Evans, Los Angeles, Dorothy Dalton (Box 139, Folder 1822)
      - Foss and Halsey, San Francisco, Circus Performers (Box 139, Folder 1823)
      - Franklin, J. G., Redding, Hanging of the Ruggles Brothers, 1892 (Box 139, Folder 1824)
      - Hartsook, Fred, Los Angeles and San Francisco, May Allison (Box 139, Folder 1825)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Alice Oates (Box 139, Folder 1826)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, "Baby Belmont" (Box 139, Folder 1827)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Carro True (Box 139, Folder 1828)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Dolly Adams (Box 139, Folder 1829)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Helena Modjeska (Box 139, Folder 1830)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Jeffreys Lewis (Box 139, Folder 1831)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Jennie Lee (Box 139, Folder 1832)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Louise Montague (Box 139, Folder 1833)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Louise Searle (Box 139, Folder 1834)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Mabel Santley (Box 139, Folder 1835)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Maud Moore (Box 139, Folder 1836)
      - Houseworth, San Francisco, Viola Clifton (Box 139, Folder 1837)
      - Johnson, George H., San Francisco, R. C. Gridley (Box 139, Folder 1838)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Georgie Cooper (Box 139, Folder 1839)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Jessie Wyatt (Box 139, Folder 1840)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Lillian Russell (Box 139, Folder 1841)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, May Brookyn (?) (Box 139, Folder 1842)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Thin man with a cane (Box 139, Folder 1843)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Two men with beards (Box 139, Folder 1844)
      - Jones & Lotz, San Francisco, Large man with a cane (Box 139, Folder 1845)
      - Levin's Book Store, San Francisco, Adelaide Neilson (Box 139, Folder 1846)
      - Marceau, Theodore C., San Francisco, "Chiquita" (Box 139, Folder 1847)
      - Marceau, Theodore C., San Francisco, Gertie Cochran, "The Mental Wonder" (Box 139, Folder 1848)
      - Marceau, Theodore C., San Francisco, David Kalakaua, King of Hawaii (Box 139, Folder 1849)
      - Moulin, Gabriel, San Francisco, Eight women in Fireman's Fund uniforms, 1943 May (Box 139, Folder 1850)
      - Parker & Co., Los Angeles, G. A. Dobinson, 1880 June (Box 139, Folder 1851)
      - Shew, William, San Francisco, Grace Egerton, wife of George Tinkler Case (Box 139, Folder 1852)
      - Shew, William, San Francisco, Thomas Starr King (Box 139, Folder 1853)
      - Shew, William, San Francisco, Man with mustache in uniform (Box 139, Folder 1854)
      - Spooner, Stockton, "Monsieur Joseph, The French Giant" (Box 139, Folder 1855)
      - Spooner, Stockton, Woman standing, Zaber da Lute (Box 139, Folder 1856)
      - Sunbeam Art Gallery, Los Angeles, Reverend Will A. Knighten (Box 139, Folder 1857)
      - Swasey, Frederick P., San Francisco, "Major and Mrs. Pay," little people (Box 139, Folder 1858)
      - Taber, L. W., San Francisco, Mollie Brown (Box 139, Folder 1859)
      - Thors, Louis, San Francisco, Hope Ross (Box 139, Folder 1860)
      - Tuttle, W. N., Stockton, "Monsieur Joseph, The French Giant" (Box 139, Folder 1861)
      - Winberg, J. A., San Francisco, Little person with mustache in uniform (Box 139, Folder 1862)
      - Unidentified photographer, San Diego, Ephraim W. Morse (Box 139, Folder 1863)
      - Unidentified photographer, San Francisco, James D. Phelan (Box 139, Folder 1864)
      - Unidentified photographer, Northern California, Fireman's Fund Baseball team (Box 139, Folder 1865)
    - Kansas
      - Nixon, John, Wellington, nine portraits of men, probably journalists (Box 139, Folder 1866)
    - Massachusetts
      - Fuller & Smith, Boston, Abraham Lincoln (Box 140, Folder 1867)
      - Green, Frederick, Boston, Baseball team (Box 140, Folder 1868)
      - Taber, Charles, New Bedford, "Shakespeare in his Study" (Box 140, Folder 1869)
    - Montana
      - Brewster, J. C., Helena, Adeline Ross (Box 140, Folder 1870)
    - New Jersey
      - The Alfred Camprell Art Company, Elizabeth, "Little Butterfly, Posed by Elvelyn Nesbit" (Box 140, Folder 1871)
      - Wendt, Boonton, Alpine Blitch, "The Florida Fat Girl" (Box 140, Folder 1872)
    - New York
      - Brady, New York, John Parker Hale (Box 140, Folder 1873)
      - Campbell Studios, New York, Milton Sills (Box 140, Folder 1874)
      - D. Appleton & Co., New York, "Prince Imperial" (Box 140, Folder 1875)
      - E. & H. T. Anthony & Co., New York, "Admiral Dot," little person (Box 140, Folder 1876)
      - E. & H. T. Anthony & Co., New York, Charles Stratton, Lavinia Warren Stratton, and Minnie Warren (Box 140, Folder 1877)
      - E. & H. T. Anthony & Co., New York, Giant Woman (Box 140, Folder 1878)
      - Donovan, New York, Chauncey Olcott, "The Irish Tenor" (Box 140, Folder 1879)
      - Fall, E., New York, Margaret Mather (Box 140, Folder 1880)
      - Gurney & Son, New York, Miss Minnie Gray (Box 140, Folder 1881)
      - Gurney & Son, New York, Two boys in matching outfits (Box 140, Folder 1882)
      - Kern Bros., New York, Fannie Davis (Box 140, Folder 1883)
      - Launey, New York, W. J. Scanlan and girl (Box 140, Folder 1884)
      - Lumiere, New York, Clara Kimball Young, 1916 (Box 140, Folder 1885)
      - Morrill, Little Valley, Theodore Nicklas (Box 140, Folder 1886)
      - New York Photographic Co., New York, Charles and Lavinia Stratton's wedding party (Box 140, Folder 1887)
      - Sarony, New York, Harold Lockwood (Box 140, Folder 1888)
      - Sarony, New York, Laura Schirmer Mapleson (Box 140, Folder 1889)
      - Sarony, New York, Pauline Hall (Box 140, Folder 1890)
      - Wendt, New York, "Waino and Plutaino, Wild Men of Borneo" (Box 140, Folder 1891)
      - Unidentified photographer, New York, Amelita Galli-Curci (Box 140, Folder 1892)
      - Unidentified photographer (possibly Moody), New York, Mary Pickford (Box 140, Folder 1893)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Swords Bros., York, "Count Magri, Countess Magri, and Baron Magri" (Box 140, Folder 1894)
      - White, H. E., Philadelphia, Miss Dickie Lingard (Box 140, Folder 1895)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - Brady, Mathew B., Washington, D.C., Mary Todd Lincoln, 1862 (Box 140, Folder 1896)
    - Outside of the United States
      - Disdéri, André-Adolphe-Eugène, Paris, Napoleon III and Empress Eugenie (Box 140, Folder 1897)
      - Liebert, Alphonse, Paris, John C. Fremont (Box 140, Folder 1898)
      - Liebert, Alphonse, Paris, Leon Gambetta (Box 140, Folder 1899)
      - London Stereoscopic & Photographic Company, Charles Dickens (Box 141)
        Housed in a contemporary wooden frame
      - Mayall, London, Prince of Wales (Box 140, Folder 1900)
      - Mayall, London, Royal Family (Box 140, Folder 1901)
      - Soley, Gloucester, Lucy Bowly (Box 140, Folder 1902)
    - Unidentified Location
      - Jaeger, C., Fromental Halévy (Box 140, Folder 1903)
      - Kramer, P., Oliver Goldsmith (Box 140, Folder 1904)
      - Witz, Bessie Barriscale (Box 140, Folder 1905)
      - Woechener, A. C., "Chiquita" (Box 140, Folder 1906)
    - Unidentified Photographers
      Arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - Beebe, Gracie (Box 140, Folder 1907)
      - Maude Branscombe (Box 140, Folder 1908)
      - Clark, Galen, and George Fiske (Box 140, Folder 1909)
      - Dana, Viola (Box 140, Folder 1910)
      - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Box 140, Folder 1911)
      - Farnum, William (Box 140, Folder 1912)
      - Fern, Fanny (Box 140, Folder 1913)
      - Gounod, Charles (Box 140, Folder 1914)
      - Hart, William S. (Box 140, Folder 1915)
      - King, Thomas Starr (Box 140, Folder 1916)
      - LeConte, Joseph (Box 140, Folder 1917)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, and his family (Box 140, Folder 1918)
      - Mansfield, Helen Josephine (Box 140, Folder 1919)
      - Mayo, Edna (Box 140, Folder 1920)
      - Peralta, Luis María (Box 140, Folder 1921)
      - Ruskin, John (Box 140, Folder 1922)
      - Tilden, Samuel J. (Box 140, Folder 1923)
      - Tolstoy, Leo (Box 140, Folder 1924)
      - Walsh, George (Box 140, Folder 1925)
      - Unidentified woman (Box 140, Folder 1926-1929)
      - Unidentified man (Box 140, Folder 1930-1931)
  - Photographic Prints of Children
    This subseries includes photographs of children compiled by Palmquist.
    Organized under three headings: Identified Photographers, Unidentified Photographers, and Copy Photographs.
    - Identified Photographers
      Arranged alphabetically by photographer.
      - Abbett, E. R.; Flora, Illinois (Box 142, Folder 1932)
      - Abbott, J. H.; Albany, New York (Box 142, Folder 1933)
      - Alexander, J. B.; East Birmingham, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1934)
      - Baldwin's; Wichita, Kansas (Box 142, Folder 1935)
      - Barnes and Son; London, England (Box 142, Folder 1936)
      - Barnes and Evans; Snohomish, Washington (Box 142, Folder 1937)
      - Barnes, A. J.; Glenwood, Missouri (Box 142, Folder 1938)
      - Barnett; Crowley, Louisiana (Box 142, Folder 1939)
      - Beals, H. C.; Mexico, New York (Box 142, Folder 1940)
      - Beardsley, J.; Ithaca, New York (Box 142, Folder 1941)
      - Bergstresser; Renovo, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1942)
      - Best, William; Chariton, Iowa (Box 142, Folder 1943)
      - Blatt, C. G.; Bernville, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1944)
      - Bradley and Rulofson; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1945)
      - Brandmo and Poore; Britton, South Dakota (Box 142, Folder 1946)
      - Britt, P.; Jacksonville, Oregon (Box 142, Folder 1947)
      - Bronk, L. R.; Ballston Spa, New York (Box 142, Folder 1948)
      - Burgert, S. P. (Box 142, Folder 1949)
      - Butler, George W.; Bath, Maine (Box 142, Folder 1950)
      - Calvert, J. P.; Mooresville, Indiana (Box 142, Folder 1951)
      - Central Atelieret; Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 142, Folder 1952)
      - Chambay; Paris, France (Box 142, Folder 1953)
      - Clark, E. L.; Watsonville, California (Box 142, Folder 1954)
      - Clausen, Emil; Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 142, Folder 1955)
      - Cobb's Gallery; Grass Valley, California (Box 142, Folder 1956)
      - Cobb's (Doré Gallery); San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1957)
      - Cook, W. B.; Colusa, California (Box 142, Folder 1958)
      - Cook, W. H.; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1959)
      - Cooper, P. F.; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1960)
      - Cramer, C. L.; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1961)
      - Cramer, D.; Antwerp, Ohio (Box 142, Folder 1962)
      - Dames; Oakland, California (Box 142, Folder 1963)
      - Dames and Butler; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1964)
      - Dames and Hayes; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1965)
      - Davidson, N. R. (Box 142, Folder 1966)
      - Dean; Sacramento, California (Box 142, Folder 1967)
      - Doncaster, J.; Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1968)
      - Donnan; Ponca City, Oklahoma (Box 142, Folder 1969)
      - Doran; Tulare, California (Box 142, Folder 1970)
      - Dowe (Box 142, Folder 1971)
      - Dunham, H. E.; Marshall, Michigan (Box 142, Folder 1972)
      - Dunham, Murry; Vallejo, California (Box 142, Folder 1973)
      - Dunshee and Weld; Aurora, Illinois (Box 142, Folder 1974)
      - Dyeau and Severin; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1975)
      - The Eagle Studio; Chicago, Illinois (Box 142, Folder 1976)
      - Edouart, A.; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1977)
      - Edouart and Cobb; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1978)
      - Felt, L. W.; Chicago, Illinois (Box 142, Folder 1979)
      - Ferrand, Charles; Nevada, California (Box 142, Folder 1980)
      - Fordtran; Blue Island, Kensington, and Riverdale, Illinois (Box 142, Folder 1981)
      - Foss, Oscar; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1982)
      - Fowzer, J.; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1983)
      - Frank's; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1984)
      - Fredricks, C. D.; New York, New York (Box 142, Folder 1985)
      - Fuller; San Francisco, California (Box 142, Folder 1986)
      - Garner, A.; Waverly, Iowa (Box 142, Folder 1987)
      - Gehres, F. J.; The Dalles, Oregon (Box 142, Folder 1988)
      - Gilbert, G. H.; Placerville, California (Box 142, Folder 1989)
      - Glendenning; Madison, South Dakota (Box 142, Folder 1990)
      - Gill's City Gallery; Lancaster, Pennsylvania (Box 142, Folder 1991)
      - Goss, E. L.; Waltham, Massachusetts (Box 142, Folder 1992)
      - Halsey; Grass Valley, California (Box 142, Folder 1993)
      - Hansen, Theodor; Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 142, Folder 1994)
      - Haussler, F. O.; Oakland, California (Box 142, Folder 1995)
      - Healy, E. R.; Hanford and Lemoore, California (Box 143, Folder 1996)
      - Heller, L.; Fort Jones, California (Box 143, Folder 1997)
      - Higgins; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 1998)
      - Holler; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 1999)
      - Howell; Yreka, California (Box 143, Folder 2000)
      - Hucks, J. G.; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2001)
      - Imperial; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2002)
      - Irvin, George C.; Dixon, California (Box 143, Folder 2003)
      - Jacobs, J. M.; Auburn, California (Box 143, Folder 2004)
      - Johnson; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2005)
      - Johnson, B. R.; Petaluma, California (Box 143, Folder 2006)
      - Johnson, George; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2007)
      - Jones, Daniel; Liverpool, England (Box 143, Folder 2008)
      - Jones, Robinson and Company; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2009)
      - Judkins and Tucker; Santa Clara, California (Box 143, Folder 2010)
      - Kay, W.; Jackson, California (Box 143, Folder 2011)
      - Keller; Stockton, California (Box 143, Folder 2012)
      - Kemp, J. C.; California, Sacramento (Box 143, Folder 2013)
      - Kindler, F.; Newport, Rhode Island (Box 143, Folder 2014)
      - King and Bailey; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2015)
      - Kingsley, J. L.; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2016)
      - Knighton, A.; Rhyl, Wales (Box 143, Folder 2017)
      - Lainer, Charles; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2018)
      - Lamprecht; New York, New York (Box 143, Folder 2019)
      - Lawrence and Son; Los Angeles, California (Box 143, Folder 2020)
      - Landy; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 143, Folder 2021)
      - Lawson and Powers; Los Angeles, California (Box 143, Folder 2022)
      - Leftwich and Harkness; Sacramento, California (Box 143, Folder 2023)
      - Lewis; San Luis Obispo, California (Box 143, Folder 2024)
      - Ley, T. A.; Woodland, California (Box 143, Folder 2025)
      - Lidberg, A.; Ishpeming, Michigan (Box 143, Folder 2026)
      - Loryea Brothers; San Jose, California (Box 143, Folder 2027)
      - Lukins, W. W.; Woodland, California (Box 143, Folder 2028)
      - Luther, H.; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2029)
      - Marceau, Theo C.; San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2030)
      - Marston, C. A.; Carson City, Nevada (Box 143, Folder 2031)
      - Masters; Princeton, Illinois (Box 143, Folder 2032)
      - Maxwell Brothers; Healdsburg, California (Box 143, Folder 2033)
      - Mayes; Bloomington, Illinois (Box 143, Folder 2034)
      - McCafferty; Stockton, California (Box 143, Folder 2035)
      - McCord, A. (Box 143, Folder 2036)
      - McCrary; Marysville, California (Box 143, Folder 2037)
      - McCullagh, E. J.; Stockton, California (Box 143, Folder 2038)
      - McMillan; Vallejo, California (Box 143, Folder 2039)
      - Melander, M.; Chicago, Illinois (Box 143, Folder 2040)
      - Merker, F. B.; Belleville, Illinois (Box 143, Folder 2041)
      - Miller, S. R.; Dudley, Pennsylvania (Box 143, Folder 2042)
      - Miller, William P.; Sacramento, California (Box 143, Folder 2043)
      - Monaco, M.; Stockton and San Francisco, California (Box 143, Folder 2044)
      - Moore; Nevada City, California (Box 143, Folder 2045)
      - Moore, E. W.; Portland, Oregon (Box 143, Folder 2046)
      - Mooers, W. A.; Salinas, California (Box 143, Folder 2047)
      - Morse, G. D.; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2048)
      - Nahl Brothers and Dickman; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2049)
      - Nast; San Francisco, California, and Denver, Colorado (Box 144, Folder 2050)
      - Nelson, Alfred; London, England (Box 144, Folder 2051)
      - Nelson, C. A.; Bakersfield, California (Box 144, Folder 2052)
      - Noble, S. S.; North San Juan, California (Box 144, Folder 2053)
      - Novelty Studio; Santa Cruz, California (Box 144, Folder 2054)
      - Olsen, H.; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2055)
      - Ormsby; Stockton, California (Box 144, Folder 2056)
      - Payne; Sacramento, California (Box 144, Folder 2057)
      - Peters, J. H.; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2058)
      - Piggott, J. K.; Santa Rosa, California (Box 144, Folder 2059)
      - Pioneer Gallery; Stockton, California (Box 144, Folder 2060)
      - Porter, D. A.; Santa Rosa, California (Box 144, Folder 2061)
      - Price, Andrew; Napa, California (Box 144, Folder 2062)
      - Preuniger, A. L.; Vlissingen and Zierikzee, Netherlands (Box 144, Folder 2063)
      - Quirk, James; Grass Valley, California (Box 144, Folder 2064)
      - Ramsdell and Bacon; Ballston Spa, New York (Box 144, Folder 2065)
      - Rankin, Frank A.; Eugene City, Oregon (Box 144, Folder 2066)
      - Reed, J. Q.; Petaluma, California (Box 144, Folder 2067)
      - Reed, N. H.; Santa Barbara, California (Box 144, Folder 2068)
      - Reese Art Parlors; Santa Cruz, California (Box 144, Folder 2069)
      - Reilly, J. J.; Marysville, California (Box 144, Folder 2070)
      - Reinhart, J. D.; Red Bluff, California (Box 144, Folder 2071)
      - Rendall, S. A.; Santa Rosa, California (Box 144, Folder 2072)
      - Ribelin, W. H.; Ellensburg, Washington (Box 144, Folder 2073)
      - Rieman and Company; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2074)
      - Rule, E. L.; St. Helena, California (Box 144, Folder 2075)
      - Schoene, H.; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2076)
      - Schumacher; Los Angeles, California (Box 144, Folder 2077)
      - Schuman and Bruner; California (Box 144, Folder 2078)
      - Seavey's; Canton, Illinois (Box 144, Folder 2079)
      - Selleck, Silas; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2080)
      - Sewell, D; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2081)
      - Shaw, William; Santa Rosa, California (Box 144, Folder 2082)
      - Shew, Jacob; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2083)
      - Shew, William; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2084)
      - Silva, J. T.; San Francisco, California (Box 144, Folder 2085)
      - Simas; Placerville, California (Box 144, Folder 2086)
      - Simpson (Box 144, Folder 2087)
      - Sisson, E. R.; Great Barrington, Massachusetts (Box 144, Folder 2088)
      - Smith; Oakland, California (Box 144, Folder 2089)
      - Smith, J.; West Oakland, California (Box 144, Folder 2090)
      - Smith, J. G.; Vallejo, California (Box 144, Folder 2091)
      - Snodgrass; Astoria, Oregon (Box 144, Folder 2092)
      - Snyder, R. W.; Columbus, Indiana (Box 144, Folder 2093)
      - Sommer, Herm.; Hamm, Germany (Box 144, Folder 2094)
      - Spooner, J. C.; Springfield, Massachusetts (Box 144, Folder 2095)
      - Spooner, J. Pitcher; Stockton, California (Box 144, Folder 2096)
      - Steckel, George; Los Angeles, California (Box 144, Folder 2097)
      - Stinson, Lewis J.; Marysville, California (Box 145, Folder 2098)
      - Stuart, W. M.; Stockton, California (Box 145, Folder 2099)
      - Sutterley and Dart; Pacheco, California (Box 145, Folder 2100)
      - Swart, J.; Nevada City, California (Box 145, Folder 2101)
      - Taber, J. W. and Company; San Francisco, California (Box 145, Folder 2102)
      - Tenney, Charles A.; Winona, Minnesota (Box 145, Folder 2103)
      - Thwaites; Portland, Oregon (Box 145, Folder 2104)
      - Todd, John A.; Sacramento, California (Box 145, Folder 2105)
      - Townsend, T. W.; Iowa City, Iowa (Box 145, Folder 2106)
      - Tresize, W. C.; Fairbury, Illinois (Box 145, Folder 2107)
      - Variell, J. S.; Gardiner, Maine (Box 145, Folder 2108)
      - Vaughn; San Francisco, California (Box 145, Folder 2109)
      - Webster; Oakland (Box 145, Folder 2110)
      - Wells; Sonora, California (Box 145, Folder 2111)
      - Westervelt and Coules; Los Angeles, California (Box 145, Folder 2112)
      - Wax, William; California (Box 145, Folder 2113)
      - Williams and Samuels; Oakland, California (Box 145, Folder 2114)
      - Winberg, J. A.; San Francisco, California (Box 145, Folder 2115)
      - Winter; Eugene City, Oregon (Box 145, Folder 2116)
      - Wise; San Francisco, California (Box 145, Folder 2117)
      - Wolfe, S. A.; Sacramento, California (Box 145, Folder 2118)
      - Woods, D. H.; Chico, California (Box 145, Folder 2119)
      - Woods' Art & Photography; Marysville, California (Box 145, Folder 2120)
      - Wright, W. W.; San Jose, California (Box 145, Folder 2121)
      - Wykes; Grand Rapids, Michigan (Box 145, Folder 2122)
      - Wyllie, E. A. G. (Box 145, Folder 2123)
      - Zuller's; Mohawk, New York (Box 145, Folder 2124)
    - Unidentified Photographers
      Arranged alphabetically by subject followed unidentified individuals.
      - Bell, Lizzie Carlisle (Box 145, Folder 2125)
      - Hart, Thomas B. (Box 145, Folder 2126)